[
  {
    "question": "What is 9 - 2?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 - 1?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 / 5?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Japan?",
    "options": ["Beijing", "Seoul", "Tokyo", "Bangkok"],
    "answer": "Tokyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you name the capital of Missouri?",
    "options": ["Jefferson City", "Rolla", "Springfield", "Joplin"],
    "answer": "Jefferson City"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 6?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the capital of South Korea.",
    "options": ["Seoul", "Tokyo", "Beijing", "Bangkok"],
    "answer": "Seoul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 - 6?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 + 9?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What city is the capital of Thailand?",
    "options": ["Bangkok", "Phuket", "Chiang Mai", "Pattaya"],
    "answer": "Bangkok"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 21 / 3?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 - 3?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 / 9?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 - 8?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 x 7?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "56"
  }
]